Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Card games, 1993-2017; 18 boxes
  - Magic: The Gathering, 9
    - The Dark (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1994; 1 box, unopened (Box C6)
    - The Eternal Struggle (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), undated; A Players Guide to the JYHAD (Box C1)
    - The Rath Cycle: Exodus (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998; 1 box, unopened (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Exodus, "Dominator" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Exodus, "Groundbreaker" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Exodus, "White Heat" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Exodus, "Widowmaker" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Stronghold (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Stronghold, "Call of the Kor" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Stronghold, "Migraine" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, unopened, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Stronghold, "Spikes" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, unopened, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Stronghold, "The Sparkler" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Tempest, "Deep Freeze" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, unopened, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Tempest, "Flames of Rath" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Tempest, "The Slivers" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, unopened, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - The Rath Cycle: Tempest, "The Swarm" (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box, unopened, prebuilt deck (Box C11)
    - Urza's Saga (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1993; 1 box, unopened (Box C11)
    - Visions (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1996; 1 box (Box C2)
    - Weatherlight (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997; 1 box (Box C2)
  - Master Deck, 10
    - Master Deck (no city: West End Games, Ltd. ), 1994; 1 box (Box C3)
  - Middle Earth, 11
    - The Dragons (Richmond, VA: Ice Enterprises), 1 box (Box C14)
  - Mythos, 12
    - New Aeon (Oakland, CA: Chaosium, Inc. ), 1997; 1 box (Box C3)
    - New Aeon (Oakland, CA: Chaosium, Inc. ), 1997; 1 box, unopened (Box C13)
    - New Aeon (Oakland, CA: Chaosium, Inc. ), 1997; 1 box, unopened (Box C13)
    - Standard Game Set (Oakland, CA: Chaosium, Inc. ), 1996; 1 box, unopened (Box C13)
    - Standard Game Set (Oakland, CA: Chaosium, Inc. ), 1996; 1 box (Box C13)
    - Standard Game Set (Oakland, CA: Chaosium, Inc. ), 1996; 1 box (Box C13)
  - Net Runner, 13
    - Net Runner (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1996; 1 box (Box C13)
    - Net Runner (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1996; 1 box (Box C13)
  - On the Edge, 14
    - Booster Packs (Northfield, MN: Trident, Inc. ), 1994; 1 box (Box C14)
    - On the Edge (Northfield, MN: Trident, Inc. ), 1994-1995; 1 box (Box C3)
  - Shadowrun, 15
    - Shadowrun (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1997; 1 box (Box C14)
  - Sim City, 16
    - Sim City (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games), 1994; 1 box, unopened (Box C14)
    - Sim City (Niles, IL: Mayfair, Inc. ), 1995; 1 box (Box C4)
  - Spellfire, 17
    - Dragon Lance (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc. ), 1994; 1 box, unopened (Box C6)
    - Greyhawk (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc. ), 1994; 1 box, unopened (Box C6)
    - Ravenloft (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc. ), 1994; 1 box, unopened (Box C6)
  - Star Trek: The Next Generation, 18
    - Customizable Card Game (Norfolk, VA: Decipher Inc.), 1995; 1 box, Limited Edition Collector's Tin (Box C13)
  - Thief of Thieves, 19
    - Thief of Thieves (Columbus, OH: R.C. Enterprises), 1981; 1 box (Box C10)
  - Towers in Time, 20
    - Towers in Time (Kansas City, MO: Thunder Castle Games, Inc.), 1994; 1 box (Box C13)
  - Unknown, 21
    - Unknown, Assorted loose cards in envelope (Box C14)
- Miniatures, Props, and Pieces, 1980-1993; 42 boxes
  The Miniatures series consists of small playing pieces created by several companies, which were designed to be used as part of table top role-playing games. Many miniatures were deliberately generic, and were not designated for any particular brand of game. Most miniatures dating from the 1980s were very small, on a 15mm or 25mm scale, and were made with lead-based metals. Later miniatures (dating from the 1990s) were made with lead-free pewter or plastic. Players could purchase the packs of miniatures and then paint them, which along with adding color served to make the pieces more durable for long-term use.
  The miniatures in this collection represent a wide range of themes and companies. The majority of the miniatures are intended for play with dungeon-themed role-playing games. Many miniatures represent magical characters such as dragons, monsters, warriors, elves, knights, gods, or princesses. Other games represented include Traveller, Call of Cthulhu, Indiana Jones, comic superheroes from both DC Comics and Marvel Comics, The Lord of the Rings, RuneQuest, and BattleTech. The majority of the miniatures in this collection are from the Ral Partha, Grenadier Models, and Citadel Miniatures companies.
  The series consists of approximately 660 unopened packs of miniatures. Miscellaneous supplementary materials are also included in this series, such as maps, exansion sets, and blank character cards. Items have been arranged alphabetically by company, and by series within those companies.
  The series also contains hundreds of hand-painted loose miniatures, some of which were handpainted by the Murrays.
  - Advanced Squad Leader terrain boards (Box P42)
  - Archive Miniatures: Archive Miniatures, 2 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - Archive Miniatures: Archive Miniatures, 3 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Asgard Miniatures, 7 pack(s) (Box P8)
  - Black Baron, 1 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - Broadsword Miniatures, 8 pack(s) (Box P8)
  - Castle Creations: Castle Creations, 7 pack(s) (Box P2)
  - Citadel, 4 pack(s) (Box P4)
  - Citadel: Dungeons and Dragons, 1 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel Miniatures: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 20 pack(s) (Box P30)
  - Citadel Miniatures: Eternal Champion, 2 pack(s) (Box P30)
  - Citadel Miniatures: Fighter, 12 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Citadel Miniatures: Great Imperial Dragon, 1 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - Citadel Miniatures: Lord of the Rings, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Citadel Miniatures: Undead, 11 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Citadel: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 3 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 1 pack(s) (Box P27)
  - Citadel: Clear Stand, 1 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Collector Series, 7 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Dark Ages, 6 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Dark Ages, 6 pack(s) (Box P8)
  - Citadel: Dragon, 2 pack(s) (Box P27)
  - Citadel: Dungeons and Dragons, 1 pack(s) (Box P4)
  - Citadel: Dwarven Stonecut, 2 pack(s) (Box P27)
  - Citadel: Elf, 2 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Eternal Champion, 1 pack(s) (Box P4)
  - Citadel: Fantasy Adventures, 1 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Lord of the Rings, 1 pack(s) (Box P4)
  - Citadel: Monsters, 2 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Realm of Chaos, 1 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Talisman, 4 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Townsfolk and Villagers, 1 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Undead, 2 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Citadel: Warrior, 1 pack(s) (Box P3)
  - Dark Horse: Elementals, 2 pack(s) (Box P9)
  - Dark Horse: Groo, 2 pack(s) (Box P9)
  - Dragon Tooth, 15 pack(s) (Box P18)
  - FASA Corporation: BattleTech, 2 pack(s) (Box P2)
  - FASA Corporation: BattleTech, 5 pack(s) (Box P29)
    patches
  - FASA Corporation: Star Trek map, 1 pack(s) (Box P29)
  - Garrison: Greenwood and Ball, 1 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - GDW: Space 1889, 4 pack(s) (Box P32)
  - Grenadier Models: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 3 pack(s) (Box P10)
  - Grenadier Models: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 7 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 2 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Colossal Lords, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Cthulhu, 2 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Cthulu, 17 pack(s) (Box P10)
  - Grenadier Models: Dragon Lords, 15 pack(s) (Box P11)
  - Grenadier Models: Dragon Lords, 19 pack(s) (Box P14)
  - Grenadier Models: Dragon Lords, 7 pack(s) (Box P16)
  - Grenadier Models: Dragon Lords, 5 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Dragon Lords, 3 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Dragons, 1 pack(s) (Box P16)
  - Grenadier Models: Dungeon Floors, 1 pack(s) (Box P16)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Lords, 2 pack(s) (Box P5)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Lords, 8 pack(s) (Box P10)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Lords, 6 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Lords, 9 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Personalities, 6 pack(s) (Box P10)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Personalities, 6 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Personalities, 2 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Fantasy Warriors, 2 pack(s) (Box P10)
  - Grenadier Models: Heroes, 5 pack(s) (Box P5)
  - Grenadier Models: Lord of the Rings, 1 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Lord of the Rings, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Masterpiece Editions, 1 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Shadow Run, 2 pack(s) (Box P10)
  - Grenadier Models: Shadow Run, 1 pack(s) (Box P16)
  - Grenadier Models: Special Edition, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Traveller, 3 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Grenadier Models: Western Gunfighter, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Grenadier Models: Wizzards and Warriors, 3 pack(s) (Box P16)
  - Grenadier Models: Wizzards and Warriors, 1 pack(s) (Box P24)
  - Heritage: Champions, 5 pack(s) (Box P13)
  - Heritage: Dragons, 5 pack(s) (Box P13)
  - Heritage: Dungeon Dwellers, 8 pack(s) (Box P13)
  - Heritage: Fantastiques, 1 pack(s) (Box P13)
  - Heritage: Knights and Magick, 4 pack(s) (Box P13)
  - Heritage: The Great Dragon, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Judges Guild: Character Chronicle cards, 1 pack(s) (Box P29)
  - Judges Guild: Dungeon Tac cards, 1 pack(s) (Box P29)
  - Martian Metals: Dragon Slayers, 11 pack(s) (Box P23)
  - Martian Metals: RuneQuest, 3 pack(s) (Box P23)
  - Martian Metals: Traveller, 12 pack(s) (Box P23)
  - Martian Metals: Traveller, 9 pack(s) (Box P31)
  - Martian Metals: Worlds of Fantasy, 1 pack(s) (Box P23)
  - Masterpiece Miniatures, 5 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - MetalMagic Miniatures: Asterix, 3 pack(s) (Box P1)
  - Miniature Figurines: The Sword and the Flame, 4 pack(s) (Box P15)
  - Miniature Figurines: Valley of the Four Winds, 7 pack(s) (Box P15)
  - Other miniatures: Loose and Misc. Miniatures (Box P36)
    Box of loose and miscellaneous handpainted miniatures. Mostly humanoid, with some very small humanoids, and with some wild animals
  - Other miniatures: Loose and Misc. Miniatures (Box P37)
    Box of loose and miscellaneous handpainted miniatures. Small dragons, humanoids, and some wild animals. Also includes horror characters: Frankenstein, Dracula, and ghosts
  - Other miniatures: Loose and Misc. Miniatures (Box P38)
    Box of loose and miscellaneous handpainted miniatures. Large dragons, small humanoids, and wild animals.
  - Other miniatures: Loose and Misc. Miniatures (Box P39)
    Box of loose and miscellaneous handpainted miniatures. Painted by the Murray Brothers
  - Other miniatures: Loose and Misc. Miniatures (Box P40)
    Box of loose and miscellaneous handpainted miniatures. Painted by the Murray Brothers. "Scene" miniatures
  - Other miniatures: Various Game Aids, 29 pack(s) (Box P28)
    Various game aids. Game accessories provided by companies like TSR and Judges Guild to accompany RPGs. Aids vary from 3D pop up tiles to system maps.
  - Pinnacle Products: Dinosaurs, 1 pack(s) (Box P1)
  - Pinnacle Products: Fantasy Lords, 1 pack(s) (Box P1)
  - RAFM Fantasy: Fantasy Miniatures, 9 pack(s) (Box P7)
  - RAFM Fantasy: Traveller: New Era, 8 pack(s) (Box P7)
  - Ral Partha, 2 pack(s) (Box P26)
  - Ral Partha: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 41 pack(s) (Box P22)
  - Ral Partha: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 65 pack(s) (Box P33)
  - Ral Partha: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 3 pack(s) (Box P35)
    Dragon Lance
  - Ral Partha: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 4 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - Ral Partha: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 2 pack(s) (Box P35)
    Forgotten Realms
  - Ral Partha: All Things Dark and Dangerous, 19 pack(s) (Box P26)
  - Ral Partha: All Things Dark and Dangerous, 4 pack(s) (Box P30)
  - Ral Partha: All Things Dark and Dangerous, 1 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - Ral Partha: BattleTech, 2 pack(s) (Box P21)
  - Ral Partha: Chaos Wars, 2 pack(s) (Box P21)
  - Ral Partha: Children of the Night, 5 pack(s) (Box P20)
  - Ral Partha: Colonials, 5 pack(s) (Box P26)
  - Ral Partha: Dragonscale, 1 pack(s) (Box P26)
  - Ral Partha: Elf Quest, 6 pack(s) (Box P17)
  - Ral Partha: Great Dragon, 1 pack(s) (Box P21)
  - Ral Partha: Imports, 26 pack(s) (Box P20)
  - Ral Partha: Imports, 1 pack(s) (Box P21)
  - Ral Partha: Imports, 8 pack(s) (Box P32)
  - Ral Partha: Imports, 6 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - Ral Partha: Personalities, 14 pack(s) (Box P19)
  - Ral Partha: Personalities, 2 pack(s) (Box P30)
  - Ral Partha: Personalities, 3 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - Ral Partha: RuneQuest, 3 pack(s) (Box P21)
  - Ral Partha: Shadow Run, 3 pack(s) (Box P30)
  - Ral Partha: The Adventurers, 13 pack(s) (Box P25)
  - Ral Partha: Three-Stage Characters, 2 pack(s) (Box P26)
  - Reaper Miniatures: Dark Heaven, 1 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - Steve Jackson Games: Car Wars expansion sets, 2 pack(s) (Box P29)
  - Steve Jackson Games: Cardboard Heroes, 3 pack(s) (Box P1)
  - Steve Jackson Games: Cardboard Heroes, 13 pack(s) (Box P29)
  - Steve Jackson Games: Cardboard Heroes, 3 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - Superior Models: Wizards and Lizards, 1 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - Tabletop Miniatures: Laserburn, 2 pack(s) (Box P6)
  - TAG Industry, 2 pack(s) (Box P9)
  - TAG Industry: Children of Fantasy, 1 pack(s) (Box P34)
  - TAG Industry: Children of the Nile, 10 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - TAG Industry: Children of Valhalla, 2 pack(s) (Box P35)
  - Task Force Games: Swordplay!, 4 pack(s) (Box P9)
  - TSR: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 8 pack(s) (Box P12)
  - TSR: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 12 pack(s) (Box P31)
  - TSR: Classics, 2 pack(s) (Box P12)
  - TSR: DragonLance trail map, 1 pack(s) (Box P29)
  - TSR: Fantasy Figures, 1 pack(s) (Box P12)
  - TSR: Indiana Jones, 1 pack(s) (Box P12)
  - TSR: Marvel Superheroes, 3 pack(s) (Box P12)